Mosa H- Ahmed

SENIOR .NET FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I am an experienced software developer and seeking employment with a fast-growing Teams. I bring more than 4 years experience writing Code and experience in the technology industry. I'm Also Experienced In Logical Situation And Extremely Fast Learner

mosa.hasn.mosa@gmail.com

+20 115 033 8846

Haram , Giza

Egyptian

Education

South Valley University

2017

Computer Science

Very good

Information Technology Institute

2018

ITI

Very good

Skills

- C# / .Net Framework / VS Studio
- Typescript / Angular /Ionic
- HTML / CSS / JS
- Entity Framework / Sql /Xamarin Forms
- Asp Core /Asp MVC
- Design Patterns /dependacy Injection

_

Courses

- Asp Mvc Core From A To Z (Udemy)
- Design Patterns (Udemy)
- Algorithms
- Head First Clean Code

Languages

French beginner

English Fluent

Arabic Mother Tongue

Work experience

Since December 2020

Since December Senior Fullstack Developer

OneTelecom (Saudi) Cairo, Egypt

Working As .Net Fullstack Developer

- Developing Company's Main Product (WarshahTech)
- Supporting Juniors
- Developing Mobile App For WarshahTech Client (Ionic)
- Transforming Legacy Code To A professional Code Design

From June 2019 to December 2020

Full Stack .Net Developer

Right Hand Solutions (Kuwait) Egypt, Cairo

- Responsible For Developing The Web Api For Arkan App (Otlob And Souq Alike)
- Developing Smart Phone App With Ionic Platform
- Supporting Old WebForms App
- Supporting Old Desktop Apps

From January 2018 to June 2019

Full Stack .Net Developer

Hard Task (Kuwait) Kuwait, Salmiya

Worked As A Team Member Developing A lot Of Web Apps Like

- Majales (Webapp For Majles Al Oma)
- Esa'al (Social Network For Education And Smart Learning Solution)
- Bab Elkhair (Online Ecommerce Store)
- Keplar (Medical Equipment Store)

From February 2017 to January 2018

.Net Developer

MTS Inc. Alexandria, Egypt

Took The Responsibility Of Developing **Web App** And **Web Api** For

"Smart Doctor" A ERP For Hospitals

From December 2015 to January 2017

From December .Net Developer (Trainee)

2015 to January Cube Sys. Alexandria, Egypt

Trained As .Net Developer Using Asp Forms And Desktop Development

Daily Used Tools

- Visual Studio
- Sql Server
- Vs Code
- PostMan
- Github
- Azure
- StackOverFlow

Projects

Smart Doctor:

An Application For Hospital Management

Web Based And smart phone App Based on Ionic

Client: MTS Technologies

Used Technologies: Asp Core Web Api, Angular, Ionic, Sql server

.....

Arkan:

An Application For Restaurants

Web Based And smart phone App Based on Ionic

Client: RHS (Kuwait) Technologies

Used Technologies: Asp Core Web Api, Angular, Ionic, Sql server

Brief: Manage Delivery, Ordering, and online payment

Coursaty:

An Application For Learning Centers

Web Based And smart phone App Based on Ionic

Client: MTS Technologies

Used Technologies: Asp Core Web Api, Angular, Ionic, Sql server, fawry

online payment

Esa'al:

An Application For private Schools smart phone App Based on Ionic

Client: Hard Task (Kuwait)

Used Technologies: Asp Core Web Api, Angular, Ionic, Sql server, online

payment (my fatorah)

Brief: Students and teachers accounts, posting questions, Answers,

and online payment

Keblar:

An Application For Medical Center

Web Based

Client: Hard Task (Kuwait) Technologies

Used Technologies: Asp Core Web Api, Angular, Sql server.

Pharmaceta:

An OLX Clone For Medical Tools and medicine

Tools: Asp Core With C#, SQL server, angular, HTML, CSS, javascript

Client: Elsafa And Elmarwa Medical Center

Social Me:

A Facebook Clone

1. Tools: Asp.net Core Web Api, Entity Framework, Angular,

2. Client : FreeLance

<u>Jym Security System (Face Detection):</u>

A System That Detect The face Of the Visitors With Sec Can

Tools : Asp Core , Open CV Library , Entity Framework

KSE Online:

A System for Engineers to apply for working in Kuwait

Client: Ministry of interor Kuwait